

## **WORK PROFILE**

Name: - Sunaina Yadav	Phone: - 9953301481
B.Tech – Comp Science	Email: - bestsunaina28312@gmail.com

**Experience:** A dyninamic professional with **5 years** of experience in SAP –ISU BILLING And Testing in DEVELOPMENT (D92) And QUALITY (Q92).

### **Professional Experience**

- 1- *BSES Rajdhani Power Limited* (Payroll of GA Digital Web Word Pvt. Ltd.) as SAP ISU-BILLING Developer, Support executive and Testing in Development (D92) and Quality (Q92) since September 2018 to till date.
- 2- *BSES Rajdhani Power Limited* (Payroll of Nippon Data System Pvt. Ltd.) as SAP ISU-BILLING Developer, Support executive and Testing in Development (D92) and Quality (Q92) since August 2016 to August 2018.
- 3- **BSES Rajdhani Power Limited** (Payroll of M Intergraph System Pvt. Ltd.) as SAP ISU-BILLING Support executive Testing in Development (D92) and Quality (Q92) since July 2015 to July 2016.

## **Current Assignment:**

## **Client Description**

BSES (Joint Venture of BSES limited with Govt. of NCT of Delhi)
BSES engage in power distribution business in the area of central, east, south and west circle of Delhi and having 33 divisions. BSES distribute the electricity approx 34 lakhs consumer in Delhi.

#### **Roles and Responsibilities:**

## **SAP IS-U IMPLEMENTATION**

- End to End Understanding of the functional areas of business
- Business process study, Gap analysis and Business Blue print preparation
- Fit Gap Analysis to identify the gaps between the business\transactional requirements and the functionalities of the product.
- Solution paper development
- Provide customization solutions to overcome the gaps identified in Fit Gap analysis

### **Handled configuration & maintenance of Activities**

- EMMA On Production (P92)
- Configuration of Schema
- Testing on Development (D92) and Quality (Q92)
- Checking Bill of MASTERRPT TABLE On Production (P92)
- Checking Bill of ZBI NET METERPT Table
- Rigorous Testing & modification of Z developments.



# **Support and Others**

- Process of creation Bill
- Process of manual Bill calculation
- Bill Reversal (Bill doc. And full reversal)
- Adjustment Reversal and link break
- Order creation
- Create Move out Final Bill
- Reverse Move out Final Bill
- Outsort Bill doc and Print doc
- Lock reading
- Category change
- Load change

# **Professional Credentials**

- B.Tech in Computer Science And Engineering from KNIT Sultanpur (U.P) with 74.8%
- Diploma in Information Technology from Govt. Girls Polytechnic Gorakhpur (U.P) with 72.8%
- 10<sup>th</sup> from U.P Board with 67.5%

#### **Others Credentials**

MS Office, Excel, C++,C, Core Java, Oracle 11g, Networking

# Strengths & Skills

- Extensive Conceptual understanding & Analytical Skills.
- Self-starter & an effective team player.
- Quick learner and resilient with enormous energy.
- Possessing strong professional values & result oriented mindset.

### **Personal Details**

Date of Birth : 6th Sept 1992 Father's name : Kanhaiya Lal Yadav

Nationality : Indian

Marital Status : Single

Contact Number : 9953301481

Location : New Delhi, India

Date: Signature: Place: